这是荷尔蒙的关系
It's hormonal.
我的意思  平时我不会推卸 这次是女人的问题
I mean, I don't usually fall back on.. It's women's issues.
但是怎么保护孩子 装防护门什么的
But child-proofed how? Gates and stuff?
伙计 她改装了抽屉
Dude, she did the drawers.
我们甚至都不知道这生娃的事情行不行得通
We don't even know if this whole fertility thing's gonna work..
她不知给抽屉装了啥玩意儿 抽屉都打不开了
she's screwed in these little jobbies where you can't even open the drawers.
完全打不开
At all?
不 能开一寸左右 只够你把手指头伸进去
No. They open an inch, then you gotta dig your finger in.
-这真是个噩梦 -我想早晚会
- It's a nightmare. -I guess sooner or later..
是啊 太晚了 她还折腾了吊柜
Yeah, a lot later. She did the upper cabinets.
如果我们有孩子 那孩子得长到30岁才能够得着柜门
Kid will be 30 before he can reach them, assuming we have a kid.
母亲保护自己的孩子是天性的
It is natural for her to feel protective.
别这么说 你也有女人的问题
Don't even.. You have women's issues.
得了吧 你们这群人
Please. You of all people.
哦 说吧 这是个凶兆
Oh, come on. It's a jinx.
这样下去我们绝对不会有孩子的
It guarantees that we won't get pregnant.
我花了20分钟才打开那该死的柜子拿到啤酒
And it takes me about 20 minutes to get a fucking beer.
筒子们 筒子们
Guys. Guys!
Stockholm失败了
Stockholm went south.
真的 我以为他们做得不错
Seriously?I thought they were looking good.
咋回事儿
What cracked?
我还没看录像 只是听其他人都这么说
I haven't seen the footage. Word's just going around
月有阴晴圆缺 人有旦夕祸福嘛
Well, that's never been a stable scenario.
地球人都知道瑞典人不靠谱
Everyone knows you can't trust Swedes.
也就是说竞争的只剩下日本了 日本和我们
That means there's just Japan. Japan and us.
这情况也不是第一次了
It's not the first time it's come down to that.
日本之前都做得很好
Japan has a perfect record.
既然咱暂时还排老二 咱就加把劲呗
We're number two. We try harder.
如果我们失败了 那...
If we fail, then...
行了 我们从98年到现在都没有失误过
Please. We haven't had a glitch since '98.
我知道我们在干什么 Lin
We know what we're doing, Lin.
不知道的也会记下来 记在某个地方
Or we have it written down..somewhere.
你们最好不要搞砸了
You guys better not be messing around in there.
你的意思是你不参加今年的打赌了 好多钱呢
Does this mean you're not in the betting pool this year? Big money.
我的意思是 这事很关键
I'm just saying, it's a key scenario.
行了 我知道你在说什么
No, I hear what you're saying.
98年那次是化学部门出了问题不是吗
In '98, it was the chem department's fault, right?
你在哪里工作 再说一次 等等 我又想起来了 现在
Where do you work, again? Wait. It's coming back to me, now.
如果每个人都这么紧张兮兮的话 这周末日子可就难熬了
It's gonna be a long weekend if everyone's that puckered up.
你星期一晚上来吗
You wanna come over Monday night?
我要去找些电钻来拯救我的柜子
I'm gonna pick up some power drills. Liberate my cabinets.
你到底有没有在听我说话
Are you even listening to me?
林中小屋
翻译：Jojo 阿海 小嗷 冰莹落雪
校对：阿西 池塘 Jojo 小嗷
后期：Sherlyparadox
压制：EOS
二逼教授
Professor fuckwad.
你怎么还没把那混蛋的照片贴到靶子上让他万箭穿心呢
Why haven't you stuck that asshole's picture on the dartboard yet?
这事很复杂 哦 上帝
It's not that simple. Oh, my God!
-你染金发了  -很赞 是吧
- Your hair. It's blonde.- Very fabulous, no?
-不敢相信你真染了  -但是很赞 对吗
- I can't believe you did it.-But very fabulous, right?
快跟赞姐走吧 我现在对这颜色都有点不太确定了
Hurry up with the "very fabulous."I'm getting insecure about it now.
不 看起来好极了 Curt肯定会神魂颠倒
No, it looks awesome. Curt's gonna lose it.
Curt会感谢我的 你也会
Curt's gonna thank me. And so will you..
让我们烧了这张照片
while we're burning this picture.
别这样
Not ready.
真的 这不是他的错
Seriously, this isn't his fault.
你觉得哪件事不是他的错
What's not his fault?
是睡了他的学生 还是发邮件跟她分手
Fucking his student or breaking up with her by email?
我当初就知道会发生什么了
I knew what I was getting into.
哦 得了吧
Oh, please.
你知道这周末会发生什么
You know what you're getting into this weekend?
这个
This.
如果Holden真的如Curt所说那么帅...
And if Holden's as cute as Curt says he is..
或许真会发生点什么
possibly getting out of it.
这是我最不想做的事情了
That is the last thing that I want.
如果你们把这个当做相亲 我就觉得一点儿意思都没有了
If you treat this like a setup,I'm gonna have no fun at all.
我没有在逼你
I'm not pushing..
但我们要带上这个
but we're packing this!
你为什么还带着书
Which means we definitely won't have room for..
说不定会很无聊呢
What if I get bored?
看书就不无聊了
These will help?
苏联经济结构 什么的余波
Soviet Economic Structures? Aftermath of the..
别带了 我们要去湖边还要喝酒
No! We have a lake and a keg.
-不准学习了  -接着
-No more learning!  -Think fast.
动作还要再快点
Faster than that.
不好意思 不好意思 让开了
Sorry. Sorry. Move along.
-接得好  -那是Holden
-Nice!  -Is that Holden?
我们马上就下来 他刚从州立学校转过来
We'll be right down. He just transferred from State.
队里最好的接球手 是一个不错的人
Best hands on the team. He's a sweet guy.
而且他手很灵活哟
And he's good with his hands.
我正和一个妹子约会...
I'm kinda seeing this girl..
不过你的头发比她靓多了
but you're way blonder than she is.
我在想 你知道 也许...这是什么
But I was thinking, you know, maybe..What is this?
这是什么 你拿这个干什么
What.. this? What are you doing with these?
行了我懂了 我不带书了
Okay, I get it. I'll leave the books.
不 谁给你的这些 谁教你的
No, who gave you these? Who taught you about these?
你教我的 行了吧
I learned it from you, okay?
我观察你的时候学到的
I learned it from watching you!
说真的 Bennett教授 他整个课程都在讲这整本书
Seriously, Professor Bennett, he covers this whole book in his lectures.
你应该读这本
You should read this.
Gurvosky 这本书有趣多了
Gurovsky. Now this is way more interesting.
而且Bennett不知道这本书
Also, Bennett doesn't know it by heart..
他会觉得你有内涵
so he'll think you're insightful.
另外 你没穿裤子
And you have no pants.
哦 该死
Oh, shit!
-东西都装上了吗  -最好是
-That pretty much it? -Fucking better be.
你知道Jules 只是过个周末而已 又不是搬家
You know, Jules, it's a weekend, not an evacuation.
相信我 箱子里的所有东西
Trust me when I say there is nothing in those cases..
你绝对都会用得到的
you won't be glad I brought.
我这就闭嘴
I'm shutting' right up.
哦 上帝
Oh, my God.
Marty
Marty!
靠 你怎么搞的 兄弟
Fuck is wrong with you, bro?
这镇上的人 开车都不跟着感觉走
People in this town drive in a very counterintuitive manner.
这就是我要说的
That's what I have to say.
你想在监狱里过周末吗
Do you wanna spend the weekend in jail?
我们要去的是我表兄在乡下的房子
We'd all like to check out my cousin's country home.
亲爱的 这可不行
Honey, that's not okay.
统计数据显示...
Statistical fact..
警察是不会拦下开车抽大麻的人的
Cops will never pull over a man with a huge bong in his car.
为什么
Why?
他们害怕呗 他们知道他看的更远...
They fear this man. They know he sees further than they..
然后他会给他们讲讲古逻辑学
and he will bind them with ancient logics.
你染了灰色头发吗
Have you gone gray?
你不能把那个东西带去Rambler
You're not bringing that thing in the Rambler.
什么
What?
烟筒放在你老爸的货车里
A giant bong in your father's van?
你怎么了 吸嗨了
What are you, stoned?
嗨 哥们
Hey, man.
Dana 你个美妞
Dana, you fetching minx!
你有吃的吗
You have any food?
-准备好了吗  -是的
-Everybody ready?  - Yeah!
-真的  -OK 我准备好了
-Yeah?  - Okay, I'm ready!
让我们出发吧
Let's get this show on the road!
倾巢而出 时间正好
Nest is empty. We're right on time.
我希望我们没开错路
I hope this is the right road.
GPS上都没显示
It doesn't even show up on the GPS.
这个全球定位屁用都没有
It is unworthy of global positioning.
这才是重点 不走寻常路
That's the whole point. Get off the grid, right?
没手机信号
No cell phone reception..
没交通摄像头
no traffic cameras.
去一个他们全球定位都没法找到我的地方..
Go someplace for one goddamn weekend where they can't..
嗨一个周末
globally position my ass, man.
这才是重点
This is the whole issue.
Marty 社会分崩离析了吗
Is society crumbling, Marty?
不 社会在凝聚 对吧
No. Society is binding. Right?
用水泥把各种坑填满
It's filling in the cracks with concrete.
什么事情都被记录 存档 写在部落格上 对吗
Everything's filed or recorded or blogged, right?
给孩子装上芯片 这样他们就不会走丢了
Chips in our kids' heads so they won't get lost.
社会需要离散
Society needs to crumble.
我们都太渺小了 只能随波逐流
We're all just too chicken-shit to let it.
我想念你的激情演说
I've missed your rants.
你总有一天会明白我说的话的
You will come to see things my way.
请出示身份
Identification, please.
Sitterson先生
Mr. Sitterson.
-Hadley先生  -多谢
-Mr. Hadley.  - Thank you.
-你叫什么  -Daniel Truman 长官
-What's your name?  -Daniel Truman, sir.
这不是军队 别叫我长官
This isn't the military. You can drop the "sir".
但是Sitterson先生喜欢被称为"女士"
But Sitterson does like to be called "ma'am."
-或者甜心  -他也会回应"甜心"的
-Or "honey toes."  -He'll also answer to "honey toes."
你清楚这里要做什么了吗
You clear on what's gonna be happening here?
我做好了准备 充足的
I've been prepped. Extensively.
他们告诉过你这里的准备与别处是不同的了吗
Did they tell you that being prepped is not the same as being prepared?
他们跟我说了 我会尽责的 Hadley先生
They told me.I'll hold my post, Mr. Hadley.
非常好
Good man.
ok 系统登上了
Okay. System's online.
搜寻目标 让我们看看情况如何了
Acquiring target.Let's see what we got.
我想他们这里不能刷卡
I'm thinking this thing doesn't take credit cards.
我觉得他们连钱都没见过
I don't think it knows about money.
大概是以物换油
I think it's barter gas.
有人吗
Hello?
嗨 Holden
Hey, Holden.
-Holden  -我觉得这里没...
-Holden!  -I don't think there's gonna be..
-你不请自入了 -我勒个去
-You come here uninvited?- Fuck!
我们打烊了
Sign says "closed."
我们想加点油
Yeah, we were looking to buy some gas.
这个泵能用吗
Does this pump work?
如果你会用的话
If you know how to work it.
我们还想问问路
We also wanted to get directions.
我们想去...那地方叫什么
We're looking for.. What's it called?
Tillerman路 请问是这个方向吗
Tillerman Road.Do you know if it's this way?
Tillerman路一直通到那边山上
Tillerman Road takes you up the hill, there.
尽头在老Buckner那儿
Dead-ends at the old Buckner place.
我表哥在那里买了个房子
My cousin bought a house up there.
通过穿山隧道 就有个湖在那儿
You go through a mountain tunnel,there's a lake.
-那地方... -Buckner
-Would that be the... - Buckner place.
一直有人想卖掉那个地方
Always someone looking to sell that plot.
你认识之前的主人吗
You knew the original owners.
见过啊 但不是第一任
Yeah, not the first.
我看到很多人来了又去 见鬼 我从战争时期就一直在这里
I seen plenty come and go. Hell, I been here since the war.
-哪场战争 -你妥妥儿的知道哪一场
- Which war?- You know damn well which war!
是有点蓝有点灰的那场吗
Would that have been with the blue and some in gray?
也许是兄弟之间打仗(南北战争)
Brother, perhaps, fighting against brother in that war?
你在逗我玩儿吗 小子
You sassing me, boy?
你对我的朋友很粗鲁
You were rude to my friend.
那个妓女
That whore?
-你说什么  -我们油加够了
-What'd you say?  -I think we got enough gas.
去程的油是够了
You got enough to get you there.
回程.
Getting back..
才是你们要担心的
that's your concern.
好了 祝你生意兴隆 先生
Well, good luck with your business, sir.
不过我想火车很快就要通到这儿来了
I know the railroad's coming through here any day, now.
那可就大件事了
That's gonna be big.
路会被铺得平平的
Streets paved with actual street.
混蛋
Fucker.
就是这里了
This must be it.
哦上帝 这还真是 美啊
Oh, my God. It's.. beautiful.
要是有蜘蛛我就在车上过夜
One spider and I'm sleeping in the Rambler.
我说真的
I mean it.
过来 帮我一把
Come on. Give me a hand.
这太棒了
This is awesome.
真酷
It is kind of cool.
你准备宰一只浣熊给我们吃吗
You gonna kill us a raccoon to eat?
我要用它的皮做顶帽子
I will use its skin to make a cap.
各位穿上泳衣 10分钟后去湖边
Everybody get your suits on. In 10 minutes, we're heading to the lake.
好
Yeah.
之前没人告诉我有这种热身活动啊
I was not informed there would be calisthenics.
是 我也不觉得
Yeah, I don't think so.
哇
Whoa.
不会吧
No way.
啊 见鬼
Ah, shit.
真脱了
This is happening.
停手
Hold up!
你肯定在跟我开玩笑
You've gotta be fucking kidding me.
这真吓人
That's just creepy.
在早期开拓时期
It was pioneer days.
人们得自己做间审讯室
People had to make their own interrogation rooms.
你表哥是从谁手里买的这个房子
Who did your cousin buy this place from?
我们该去看看其他房间 确保这是唯一一间这样的屋子
We should check the rest of the rooms, make sure this is the only one.
因为指不定Marty想偷窥我们那个
Cause you know Marty wants to watch us pounding away.
我连听都不想听
I didn't even like hearing that.
我们换房间吧
How about we switch?
不是因为我想被看
Not that I'd..
我的意思是我会把画挂回去 不过我们换房间的话 也许你会感觉好点
I mean, I'd put the picture back but you might feel better if we switched rooms?
那就最好了
I really would.
谢谢你 尊重我
Thanks. For being decent.
这是最起码的
It's the least I could do..
Curt和Jules想把我们凑一对
since Curt and Jules sold you to me for marriage.
他们都是粗神经的
They're not subtle.
好吧 我还是感到荣幸 然后自己乐乐就好了
Well, I'll just be flattered and keep it to myself.
我没有想找...
Yeah, I'm not looking for..
但 还是谢谢你没偷窥我
But, I'm still grateful that you're not a creep.
嗨 我们先别把话说死
Hey, let's not jump to any conclusions there.
我内心挣扎了很久 要不要在镜子前看着你
I had kind of an internal debate about showing you the mirror.
纠结很久 内心流血
Shouting on both sides. Blood was spilled.
所以你内心流血了
So, you're bleeding internally?
受了重伤
Pretty bad.
Jules在念医学预科 你可以让她帮帮你
Well, Jules is pre-med. You should probably talk to her.
好的
Okay.
哇
Wow.
好吧 这样也不太好
Yeah, I don't think so.
各就各位
Places everyone.
直播了
We are live.
工程师 有人换房间了
Engineering, we got a room change.
Polk在2号 McCrea在4号
Polk is now in two, McCrea is in four.
控制台听到吗 我们需要调整一下
Operations, do you copy? We need a scenario adjustment.
Lin小姐
Miss Lin.
Louden的血样报告出来了 她情况不错
We've got the blood work back on Louden. Her levels are good.
我们建议再增加5毫克Rhohyptase药剂
But we're recommending a fifty-milligram bump..
来达到催情效果
of Rhohyptase to increase libido.
-可以 -你是想要注射还是口服
- Sold. - Do we pipe it in,or do you wanna do it orally?
再问我一次 慢一点
Ask me that again, only slower.
你个猪
You're a pig.
猜猜我们是如何不让他们发觉的
Guess how we're slowing down cognition.
我不知道
I don't know.
染发剂
The hair dye.
金发无脑女 非常风雅
Dumb blonde. Very artistic.
药性从头发到血液 通过脑部 循序渐进
Works its way into the blood,through the scalp. Very gradual.
化学部门干的不错
Chem department keeps their end up.
我要看到效果才能确定
I'll see it when I believe it.
-控制台  -是的 说吧
Control?- Yeah, go ahead.
2号线通报员要跟你通话
I have the harbinger on line two.
哦上帝 就不能让他留言吗
Oh, Christ. Can you take a message?
我想不行 他听起来很急
I don't think so. He's really pushy.
老实说 他有点吓到我了
To be honest,he's kind of freaking me out.
好 接进来
Okay. Put him on.
Mordecai 亲爱的 怎么啦 上面天气如何啊
Mordecai, baby, what's happening? How's the weather up top?
羊群已经通过大门 进入屠宰场了
The lambs have passed through the gate.They are come to the killing floor.
好的 干得不错
Well, you're doing a great job out there.
按原计划进行哦亲 你这开头不错
By the numbers, man.You got us started off just right.
那么 等会跟你聊 好吗
So, we'll talk to you later, okay?
他们盲目的双眼看不到恐惧的到来
Their blind eyes see nothing of the horrors to come.
他们什么都听不见
Their ears are stopped.
好吧 他们本来就这么蠢啊
Well, that's.. how it works.
净化他们 净化这个世界的无知和罪恶
Cleanse them. Cleanse the world of their ignorance and sin.
让他们浸淫在深红的...
Bathe them in the crimson of..
你用了免提吗
Am I on speakerphone?
不 当然没有
No. Absolutely not.
扬声器 不 不 我不会那么做
Speakerphone, no.No, I wouldn't do that.
是的 我听见回音了
Yes, I am. I can hear the echo.
哦 上帝 你说对了 稍等一下 我换成听筒
Oh, my God. You're right.Hang on one second, I'll take you off.
真没礼貌 我不知道还有谁在听
That's rude.I don't know who's in the room.
好了好了 免提关了
Fine. There. You're off.
谢谢
Thank you.
别把这个当儿戏
Don't take this lightly, boy.
这并不是全由你说了算的
It wasn't all by your numbers.
这个傻瓜差点用他的傲慢无礼破坏了祷告
The fool nearly derailed the invocation with his insolence.
古老的生物能洞悉一切
The ancient ones see everything.
他们不会...
And they will not be..
你还在用免提是吗
I'm still on speakerphone, aren't I?
哦上帝啊 Mordecai
Oh, my God. Mordecai.
我真不敢相信 我又按错了
I can't believe it. I did it again!
Mordy
Mordy?
接下来会怎么样
What happens next?
哦 好冷啊
Oh! That's cold!
有多冷 值得我跳下去吗
How cold? Is it worth it?
来吧 Jules 人生就该冒险
Come on, Jules. Life is risk.
是啊 我还是在太阳下躺会吧
Yeah, I might just risk lying out in the sun for a while.
呜
Boo.
-嗨 那是什么 -什么
-Hey, what is that?  -What?
在湖里 就那里
In the lake, right there.
-哦得了 -不真的 我认真的 真的有东西在那里
-Oh, come on.  - No you guys,I'm serious. Right there.
那里 那里 天啊 看起来就像是我女朋友
There! There!God, looks just like my girlfriend!
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
湖里还有别的东西
There's something else in the lake!
- 是个帅哥  - 我要杀了你
- It's a gorgeous man!- I'm gonna kill you!
别杀帅哥 我们已经濒临灭绝了
Don't kill the gorgeous man! We're endangered!
好吧 最后一次机会
All right. Last chance.
公布时间快到了 好好考虑 下注窗口即将关闭 好了
It's post time. Dig deep, people.Betting windows are closing. Okay.
好了 谁还没下注
Okay, who's still out?
我看看 工程师 研发师 电力师也在
Let's see. We got engineering,we got R&D, and we got electrical.
你看见他们选的谁了吗
Did you see who they picked?
他们简直就是把钱送出去了
They're practically giving their money away.
你真敢说啊 潜水侠
You should talk, Aquaman.
-什么意思  -没事
-What do you mean? -Ah, nothing.
好了
Okay, all right.
我都不知道我们有这种东西
I'm not even sure we have one of these.
动物学家发誓我们有
Zoology swears we do.
他们会知道的 好了 大家
They'd know. Okay. All right, people.
嘿 你选的什么
Hey, what do you got?
不 他们早就已经被选了
No, they've already been picked.
什么 不 谁选的
What? No. Who took them?
维护师
Maintenance.
维护师 他们每年都选一样的
Maintenance? They pick the same thing every year.
你想要我怎样
What do you want from me?
他们要是有创造力 就不会在维护部了
If they were creative,they wouldn't be in maintenance.
你要是想赢就得撕了它 你想换换吗
You're gonna have to split this if you win. You wanna switch?
我不知道 我不知道 你觉得呢
I don't know, I don't know.What do you think?
我最想的是 这事儿快点完
More than anything,I just want this moment to end.
不下注吗
Not betting?
我就不用了 多谢
Not for me. Thanks.
听起来有点聒噪 是吗
Seems a little harsh, doesn't it?
这只是大家的发泄
It's just people letting off steam.
这份工作可不轻松 不过那些家伙们还能挺得住
This job isn't easy,however those clowns may behave.
主管知道...他们知道楼下的这些事吗
Does the director...Do they know about this downstairs?
主管不在乎这群员工干了些什么
The director doesn't care about this stuff.
只要楼上诸事顺利
As long as everything goes smoothly upstairs.
只要这群孩子听从他们的指示
as long as the kids do as they're told.
可是结果不是都注定了吗
But then it's fixed.
不 不 不
No, no, no.
既然结果都在你掌控之中 你怎么还能下注呢
How can you wager on this when you control the outcome?
不 我们只是把他们引到地下室 从那开始就是他们自己的事儿了
No, we just get 'em in the cellar. They take it from there.
不 他们可以自由选择
No, they have to make the choice of their own free will.
不然的话这系统没法运作
Otherwise the system doesn't work.
就像那个通报员一样
It's like the harbinger.
就是这种令人毛骨悚然的老梗才好玩 特别是那种摆明了"你马上要死了"的启示
It's this creepy old fuck, practically wears a sign, "You will die."
我们为什么要把他安排进去 系统需要
Why do we put him there? The system.
他们要选择无视他...
They have to choose to ignore him..
并且他们要选择在地下室中会发生什么
and they have to choose what happens in the cellar.
是啊 我们只在游戏需要的时候插手
Yeah, we rig the game as much as we need to.
不过最后 要是他们不越界
but in the end,they don't transgress.
我们也不会惩罚他们
They can't be punished.
接下来会怎么样 Truman 你要加入吗 下注窗口就要关闭了
So what's it gonna be, Truman?You in? Window's closing.
不用了
I'm fine.
好吧
Okay.
那就这样
That's it, gang!
界线已经封锁了
The board is locked!
让我们开始狂欢吧
Oh, let's get this party started!
Let's get this party started!
干杯
There you go.
好了轮到我了
Okay, my turn.
Jules
Jules.
真心话还是大冒险
Truth or dare?
大冒险
Let's go dare.
好吧
All right.
我要让你跟人调情
I dare you to make out with..
一定要说Dana 一定要说Dana
Please say "Dana," please say "Dana."
跟那头驼鹿 那边那个
That moose, over there.
Marty
Marty..
你以前见过驼鹿吗
have you ever seen a moose before?
管他是什么神秘野兽
Whatever that mysterious beast is.
那是头狼
That's a wolf.
我生活在一个满是大麻的子宫里 不用理我
I'm living in a womb of reefer,leave me alone.
Jules
Jules..
我要让你跟那头狼调情
I dare you to make out with that wolf.
没问题
No problem.
谁
Who?
我吗
Me?
是啊 我是新来的
Well, yes, I am new in town.
你怎么知道
How did you know?
天啊 你真好
Oh, my God.That is so sweet of you to say.
实际上我刚刚才染的头发
I just colored it, in fact.
不 不 不
No, no, no.
不用发脾气
There's no need to huff and puff.
我会让你进来的
I'll let you come in.
谢谢
Thank you.
耶
Yeah.
现在
Now,...
Dana
Dana.
真心话
Truth.
这什么意思
What's that supposed to mean?
我不过是直接跳到结论罢了
I'm just skipping ahead.
你要是说大冒险
You're gonna say dare.
她肯定会让你做一件你不愿意干的事
She's gonna dare you to do something you don't like..
之后你会炸毛 然后说其实你想玩的是真心话
and then you'll puss out and say that you wanted truth all along.
真的吗
Really?
好吧 Jules
Okay, Jules.
大冒险
Dare.
那是什么鬼玩意
What the hell was that?
是地下室的门
It's the cellar door.
大概是风吹的
The wind must've blown it open.
这又说明了什么
That makes what kinda sense?
你觉得那下面有什么
What do you think is down there?
为什么我们不自己下去看看呢
Why don't we find out?
Dana
Dana.
我打赌你不敢
I dare you.
我得在这下面待多久
How long do I have to stay down here?
噢 你懂的 待到明早就行了
Oh, you know, just 'til morning.
Dana
Dana.
你还好吧
You okay?
没事
Yeah.
对不起 我只是自己吓自己
Sorry, I just scared myself.
好吧 你求救了 挑战失败
Well, you called for help. That voids the dare.
现在可以结束了
Take your top off.
什么
What?
我可没定这种规则
I don't make up the rules.
噢 上帝啊
Oh, my God.
看看这些
Look at all this.
伙计们
Guys..
我不太确定 但是这下面挺恐怖的
I'm not sure it's awesome to be down here.
伙计们
Guys?
兄弟 说真的 你表兄居然喜欢这些怪东西
Dude, seriously, your cousin is into some weird shit.
我想这些肯定不是他的
I'm pretty sure this ain't his.
也许是放镜子的那个人的呢
Maybe it was the people who put in that mirror thing.
有些东西看上去真有年代了
Some of this stuff looks really old.
很漂亮
It's beautiful.
也许我们该回楼上去
Maybe we should go back upstairs.
你们敢挑战一下回楼上去吗
I dare you all to go upstairs.
伙计们
Guys?
大伙 听听这个
Guys, listen to this.
四月四日
"April fourth.
爸爸对我发了脾气 还指责我缺乏真正的信仰
"Father was cross with me and said I lacked the true faith.
我希望我能证明自己的虔诚
"I wish I could prove my devotion..
就好像犹大和马太向那些旅行者们证实的一样
"as Judah and Matthew proved on those travelers."
那是什么
What is that?
Anna Patience Buckner日记 1903年
Diary of Anna Patience Buckner, 1903.
妈妈几乎整晚上都在尖叫
"Mama screamed most of the night.
我祈祷她能找到自己的信仰
"I prayed that she might find faith..
但当爸爸剖开她的肚子时她就没动静了
"but she only stopped when Papa cut her belly..
爸爸往里面塞了煤块
"and stuffed the coals in.
犹大在梦里告诉我
"Judah told me in my dream..
马太把他带到了暗室里 于是我想他应该被杀掉了
"that Matthew took him to the black room, so I know he is killed.
我希望我能像马太一样理解痛苦里的荣耀
"I want to understand the glory of the pain like Matthew..
但肢解尸体时他却勃起了
"but cutting the flesh makes him have a husband's bulge..
我就不会这样
"and I do not get like that."
—上帝 我们能打住么  —不 继续读
- Jesus. Can we not?  - No. Go on.
—为什么  —我想知道
- Why?  -I want to know.
我发现
"I have found it..
在最古老的那些书里 有拯救我们家族的方法
"in the oldest books, the way of saving our family.
我写字的那只胳膊断了
"My good arm is hacked up..
我希望我写的这些字能让人看得懂
"and et, so I hope this will be readable.
一个信徒会到来 对我们的灵魂布道
"That a believer will come and speak this to our spirits.
这样我们的伤痛就会恢复 伟大的痛楚又将到来
"Then we will be restored and the great pain will return."
接下来的东西都是拉丁文了
And then there's something in Latin.
好的 我他妈的就在这儿叫个停好么
Okay, I'm drawing a line in the fucking sand, here.
别把那些拉丁文也读出来
Do not read the Latin.
这他妈是怎么回事
What the fuck?
-Dolor -不 不
- Dolor..  - No, no.
-别这么没胆儿  -Curt
- Stop being a fucking baby.  - Curt!
它就是个日记
It's a diary.
它证明不了任何事
It doesn't even mean anything.
-Dana  -（拉丁文）
- Dana!  - "Dolor supervivo caro.
（拉丁文）
"Dolor sublimis caro.
"Dolor ignio annivos."
胜利者产生了
We have a winner!
女士们先生们 是Buckners
It's the Buckners, ladies and gentlemen!
Buckners胜利了
The Buckners pull a 'W'.
好了 恭喜大家 去维护部门吧
All right. That means that congratulations go to Maintenance!
谁愿意和实习生Ronald一起分享
Who share the pot with Ronald the intern.
太棒了
Yeah!
这不公平 我也选了僵尸
That's not fair. I had zombies, too.
是的 没错 你选了僵尸
Yes, you did. You had zombies.
但是这是 “凌虐农夫僵尸家族” 明白了吗
But this is "Zombie Redneck Torture Family," see?
他们完全是两个不同的物种
They're entirely separate species.
就好像大象和海象的区别
Like the difference between an elephant and an elephant seal.
明年总会有机会的
There's always next year.
他们就像从噩梦里跑出来的东西
They're like something from a nightmare.
不 他们才是一切噩梦的源头
No. They're something nightmares are from.
我们关在里面的都是来自旧世界的
Everything in our stable is remnant of the old world..
天知道是些什么玩意
courtesy of you-know-who.
怪物 魔法
Monsters. Magic.
神
Gods.
你要去习惯
You get used to it.
那你呢
Should you?
噢 抱歉兄弟
Oh, man. I'm sorry.
-他手里有贝壳  -我知道
- He had the conch in his hands.  - I know.
谁知道接下来能发生什么
A couple more minutes, who knows what might've happened?
我再也没机会见到男美人鱼了 再也没机会了
I am never gonna see a merman. Ever.
老兄 庆幸去吧
Dude, be thankful.
那玩意儿可怕极了
Those things are terrifying.
把他们弄干净都是一场噩梦
And the cleanup on them is a nightmare.
所以就是Buckners
So, the Buckners.
是的 他们也许会是崇拜疼痛 智力落后的白痴僵尸
Yeah, well, they may be zombified, pain-worshipping, backwoods idiots..
但他们是属于我们的崇拜疼痛 智力落后的白痴僵尸
But they're our zombified, pain-worshipping, backwoods idiots.
百分百的清除率
With a hundred percent clearance rate.
不错 所以我们该给日本方打电话了吗
True. So should we call Japan?
告诉他们接下来不用白忙活了
Tell them to take the rest of the weekend off?
是的 不错 他们是日本人 他们能干什么 玩儿吗
Yeah, right. They're Japanese. What are they gonna do? Relax?
我就想看看他们吃瘪的样子 哪怕就一次
I'd just like to see them fall on their asses, for once.
噢 上帝 可别开这种玩笑
Oh, God, don't even joke.
其他部门都做了无用功
Every other branch has air-balled.
操 就这样 宝贝儿
Fuck, yeah, baby.
“这可真棒”
This is so classy.
得了吧 搞得好像你就不想来一发似的
Come on, like you wouldn't want a piece of that.
我们今晚上能不讨论碎尸这件事了么
Can we not talk about people in pieces any more tonight?
你觉得孤单吗 Marty
Are you feeling lonely, Marty?
我和Marty在大学一年级可是一对呢
Marty and I were sweeties in our freshman hall.
我们就亲热过一次
We made out once.
那只戒指也不是我买的
I never did buy that ring.
但我们至今仍然
But we're still..
关系挺近
close.
我有个理论能把这些解释清楚
I have a theory about all this.
那东西能把我们从这儿弄出去吗
That's our cue to bail.
Tommy Chong想到一个理论 过来吧 宝贝儿
Tommy Chong here has a theory. Come on, baby.
别担心 你可以留着对我们的书呆子说
Don't worry, you can tell it to Egghead, here..
前提是他不忙着去泡Dana的话
if he's not too busy devirginizing Dana.
Jules 你现在就要上床去吗
Jules, do you wanna go lie down?
说到点子上了 来 我们上 上
That's exactly the point. Come on. Mush. Mush.
别推着我转圈
Don't push me around.
不转圈 宝贝儿 直奔主题
Not around, baby. Straight line.
你当真不觉得有些事情挺奇怪吗
You seriously believe nothing weird is going on?
阴谋论
Conspiracy?
每个人的表现
The way everybody's acting.
为什么Jules突然走无脑名媛风
Why is Jules suddenly a celebu-tard?
Curt又是什么时候开始热衷那些大男子主义的废话的
And since when does Curt pull this alpha-male bullshit?
我是指 他是个社会系的学生
I mean, he's a sociology major.
他拿全额奖学金
He's on full academic scholarship..
现在他却管他的朋友叫书呆子
and now he's calling his friend an egghead?
Curt只是喝醉了
Curt's just drunk.
我见识过他喝醉是什么样
I've seen Curt drunk.
Jules的也见过
Jules, too.
那么 也许 是因为别的什么原因
Well, then, maybe it's something else.
你就是不愿意承认眼前所看到的东西是吗
You're not seeing what you don't wanna see.
拉线木偶
Puppeteers.
什么
Puppeteers?
果酱馅饼
Pop-Tarts?
你刚刚提到果酱馅饼了吗
Did you say you have Pop-Tarts?
Marty 我爱你  但你真的嗨过头了
Marty, I love you,but you're really high.
我们都不是我们自己了
We are not who we are.
我得去看本有插图的书
I'm gonna go read a book with pictures.
谢谢 痛楚是超越肉体的存在
Thank you.- "The pain outlives the flesh.
“血肉回归”也有可能是“有一个集合场所”
"The flesh returns.. "or "has a meeting place."
这是什么
What is that?
你在地下室读的那些拉丁文
The Latin that you read in the basement.
你会说拉丁语
You speak Latin?
说得不好  十年纪以后就没说过了
Not well. Not since tenth grade.
奇怪的是它突然就跑回我脑子里去了
Weird how it all comes back.
好吧 这一晚可真够奇怪的
Well, it's a weird kind of night.
今晚上我很抱歉
I'm sorry about tonight.
每个人都
Everybody..
如果我告诉你我觉得今晚挺美好的你会对我印象减分吗
Do I lose points if I tell you I'm having a pretty nice time?
不 你当然可以这么说
No. You can tell me that.
你跑什么
What are you running away for?
别溅在我身上了
Don't spill on me!
我把啤酒洒在你衣服上了吗
Did I get a little beer on your shirt?
我觉得你该把它们脱下来了 对吧
I guess it'll have to come off, huh?
不是在这儿
Not here.
宝贝儿 来嘛
Baby, come on.
现在没别人了
We're all alone.
我有点儿冷
I'm chilly.
好了 大伙 就这样了  该走了 我们还有工作要做呢
Okay, guys. That's it. Let's go. We've got a job to do.
你们这些人类的原始冲动让我恶心 从这儿出去
Your basic human needs disgust me.Get out of here.
-这个区域有温度控制功能吗？ -马上调整
- Do we have temperature control in this sector? - On it.
来点迷雾帮助释放费洛蒙
Engaging pheromone mists.
这可真黑
It's so dark.
我们回屋里去
Take me inside?
噢别 就是因为黑我们才到这儿来的
Come on. This is why we came here.
这很浪漫
It's romantic.
来吧 宝贝儿 让我们看看你的胸部
Okay, baby. Let's see some boobies.
给我们验验货
Show us the goods.
我们这样看着她好么
Does it really matter if we see her..
在看这个的可不只有我们 小子
We're not the only ones watching, kid.
客户是上帝
Gotta keep the customer satisfied.
你知道在这什么最重要吧
You understand what's at stake, here?
得分
Score.
Jules
Jules!
在此我们提供谦卑和恐惧
This we offer in humility and fear.
而在永久的沉眠中将会得到被赐福的平静
For the blessed peace of your eternal slumber.
如同永恒
As it ever was.
Nemo 伙计 你该起床了 这世界全乱套了
Nemo, man, you gotta wake up.Your shit is topsy-turvy.
我要去散个步
I'm gonna go for a walk.
好吧 我他妈的发誓刚才有人说话
Okay. I swear to fucking God, somebody is talking.
我确实听见有人说话了
Or I'm pretty sure someone is.
我要去散个步
I'm gonna go for a walk.
够了
Enough!
你在说什么
What are you saying?
你到底想怎样
What do you want?
你觉得我是个人偶 哈
You think I'm a puppet, huh?
你觉得我就是个人偶 会为你了
You think I'm a puppet. Gonna do a little..
去跳什么该死的拉线舞蹈
fucking puppet dance!
我才是我自己大脑的主人 做梦去吧
I'm the boss of my own brain, so give it up.
我要去散个步
I'm gonna go for a walk.
我不想要
I don't wanna..
我的意思是 我从来不
I mean, I've never..
我不是指从没有过
I don't mean "never"..
嘿
Hey.
没什么是你不想要的
Nothing you don't want.
他勃起了
He's got a husband bulge.
我还以为这儿会有星星呢
I thought there'd be stars.
我们被抛弃了
We are abandoned.
-妈的  -妈的快跑
- Fuck!  - Fucking run!
Curt
Curt!
死女人
Dead bitch!
上帝啊 发生了什么
Jesus, what happened?
妈的
The fuck!
Curt 这他妈的是怎么回事
Curt, what the fuck?
你哪里受伤了
Where are you hurt?
这都是你的血吗
Is all of this from you?
没事了 Curt 你没事了
It's okay! Curt, you're okay!
Jules在哪里
Where's Jules?
她死了
She's gone.
我们得离开这里
We've gotta get out of here.
不 不
No. No.
Dana 别开门
Dana, don't open that..
不找到Jules我不会离开这里
I'm not leaving here without Jules.
那个死了的女人就在外面
That dead girl's out there!
Dana 过来
Dana, come on!
那是什么鬼东西
What is that thing?
妈的
Fuck!
我不知道 但是有很多
I don't know, but there's more of them.
还有很多
More of them?
我看到一个年轻女孩
I saw a young girl.
就像他一样变成了僵尸
All zombied like him..
但是她少了一条胳膊
but she was missing an arm.
哦 上帝啊 Patience
Oh, my God. Patience.
那本日记
The diary.
- 我们要把这里封锁起来  -他说的没错
- We gotta lock this place down.  -He's right.
我们一个房间接一个房间的去 堵死每扇门窗
We'll go room by room. Barricade every window and door.
我们要保证安全 不管发生什么事 我们都要在一起
We gotta play it safe. No matter what happens, we have to stay together.
妈的
Fuck!
冷静
Calm down.
看大师出马
Watch the master work.
不对劲
This isn't right.
什么 发生什么事了
What? What's the matter?
这不对 我们应该分开行动
This isn't right. We should split up.
这样我们效率更高
We can cover more ground that way.
对
Yeah.
对 好主意
Yeah. Good idea.
真的
Really?
好了 大家回到房间里去
All right, you guys, get in your rooms.
把他们锁起来
Lock them in.
这他妈的是怎么回事
What the fuck?
这他妈的
What the..?
这他妈的是什么
What the fuck?
情况不妙
That's not good.
让开 让开 让开
Out of the way. Out of the way. Out of the way.
化学部 我需要500cc的氯丙嗪
Chem department, I need 500 CCs of Thorazine..
注入三号房间
pumped into room three.
不 不 不
No, no, no.
等等 化学部
Stand by, Chem.
Judah Buckner会搞定的
Judah Buckner to the rescue.
这他妈的是什么
What the fuck?
Fuck! What the fuck?
哦 上帝
Oh, my God.
我在上电视节目
I'm on a reality TV show.
我的父母会认为我很没用的
My parents are gonna think I'm such a burnout.
救救我 救救我
Help me! Help me!
楼下一定很精彩
Must be getting excited downstairs.
全世界最精彩的演出
Greatest show on Earth.
救命啊
Somebody help!
过来
Come on!
-用床  -快 快
-Use the bed!  - Come on! Come on!
-这里是空的  -走
-It's empty.  - Go.
-Curt  -打开门
-Curt?  - Unlock the door.
我打不开 去地下室
I can't. Get down to the basement.
这里是暗室
This is the black room.
很好
Nice.
日记上写着
From the diary.
这里是他杀死他们的地方
This is where he killed them.
这里也会是他杀死我们的地方
This is where he kills us.
不会的
No way. No.
他杀不了我们
He's not gonna kill us
我们只需要找到一扇门
We just gotta find a door.
知道吗
Okay?
我们去查看一下墙 好吗
Let's just check the walls, okay?
Curt
Curt?
我说 这里总有
I mean, there's gotta be..
你喜欢痛苦吗
You like pain?
尝尝这个怎么样
How's that work for you?
这些愚蠢的僵尸
These fucking zombies.
它就不能直接把那女孩扔进火山里
Remember when you could just throw a girl in a volcano?
我又不是小孩子
How old do you think I am?
快跑 快跑 快跑
Let's move! Come on! Come on! Go!
Marty怎么办
What about Marty?
他们抓住了他
They got him.
这个魔鬼已经被打败了
The devil is defeated.
现在Kiko的灵魂会永远活在这只快乐的青蛙里
Now Kiko's spirit will live in the happy frog!
去死吧
Fuck you!
去死吧 去死吧 去死吧
Fuck you! Fuck you! Fuck you!
-你看到了吗  -完美的记录 哈
- You seeing this?  - Perfect record, huh?
那群日本小孩不应该有这个东西 她们玩了我们
The Japan crew should've had this in the bag. They fucked us.
干掉这群九岁的小孩能有多难
How hard is it to kill nine-year-olds?
零死亡率 全部白费
Zero fatality. Total wash.
你想要买到好产品 你得买美国货
You want good product, you gotta buy American.
楼下有消息吗
Any word from downstairs?
楼下的不关心日本 监督者相信我们
Downstairs doesn't care about Japan. The director trusts us.
你只是在使唤化学部 Lin
You just sweat the chem, Lin.
当这群傻瓜在唱 我们的神道教朋友 的时候
While these morons are singing What a Friend We Have in Shinto..
我们带来了痛苦
we are bringing the pain.
好吧 忽略那些 那这该死的下面是怎么回事
Yeah, and what the fuck's up with this guy's pot, anyway?
他不是应该变成僵尸流着口水 而不是差不多打败我们了
He's supposed to be drooling and instead he almost makes us?
我们太大意了
We treated the shit out of it.
好了 我们已经让这群家伙开往隧道了
Okay, we've got the Rambler heading toward the tunnel.
这群白痴要完蛋了
The fool's toast anyway.
如果你不控制好情况 我们也要完蛋了
And so are we if you don't get this under control.
-该死的  -什么 什么该死了
-Shit.  - What? "Shit" why?
该走了 有工作要做
Gotta go. Work to do.
你们是人类最后的希望 如果那些古生物
You guys are humanity's last hope. If the ancients rise..
-没有塌方  -什么
-There's no cave-in.  - What?
该死的隧道是通的
The fucking tunnel's open!
控制台呼叫爆破部
Control to Demolition.
整个区域漆黑一片
We're dark on the whole sector.
试着绕过它
Try to bypass it.
-你他妈的以为我在做什么  -开门
- What the fuck do you think I'm doing?  -Open the door.
小心 让路 快让路
Look out!  Get out of the way! Make a hole!
-他妈的出了什么事  -我们不知道
-What the fuck's going on?  - We don't know.
电力部说上面有些小故障
Electrical said there was a glitch up top.
-那个隧道几个小时之前就应该爆炸了  -我们没有收到指令
-That tunnel should've blown hours ago.  -We didn't get the order.
Hadley 出什么事了
Hadley, what is going on?
Hadley
Hadley?
隧道为什么没有炸掉
Why hasn't the tunnel blown?
不 不 这不可能
No, no. No fucking way!
我简直不敢相信 伙计 这不可能
Can't believe this, man. This ain't happening.
就发生在那里
It's right there.
好了 我们有没有攀爬工具 比如绳子
All right. We got any climbing gear? Ropes?
有 在我该死的房间里
Yeah. In my fucking dorm room.
我们不能回去
We can't go back.
没有过去的路
There's no way across.
我们该怎么办 跳吗
What're we gonna do? Jump?
老兄
Dude.
什么
What?
Curt 你确定要这么做吗
Curt, are you sure about this?
我以前跳的比这远多了
I've done bigger jumps than this.
你需要缓冲一下
You've got a smooth run..
从五英尺外的那一头可以试试
and maybe a five foot differential on the other side.
但你总得全力以赴吧
But you've gotta give it everything.
Curt
Curt.
听着 伙计们 你们留在车里
Look, you guys, you stay in the Rambler.
我会找到救援的
I'll get help.
就算我受了伤 我爬也要爬出去找救援
If I wipe out, I'll fucking limp for help.
但是我会回来
But I'm coming back here.
我会带着警察和直升机回来
I'm coming back with cops and choppers..
我还会带着大把的枪 这些鬼东西都要付出代价
and large fucking guns, and those things are gonna pay.
为了Jules
For Jules.
别犹豫
Don't hold back.
从没犹豫过
Never do.
不
No!
Curt
Curt!
哦 上帝
Oh, God!
他撞到东西了 那里什么也没有 他撞到什么了
He hit something. There's nothing. What'd he hit?
傀儡师
Puppeteers.
Marty是对的
Marty was right.
回货车里去
Get in the van.
Dana
Dana.
Marty是对的
Marty was right.
你在往回开
You're going back.
我要开出去
I'm going through.
我们要开出去 一定有另一条路
And we'll just drive. There's gotta be another road.
-另一条离开这里的路  -没用的
-Another way out of here.  -It won't work.
会有别的事情发生 会倒塌 会冲毁
Something will happen. It will collapse, it will wash away.
那我们就离开这些道路
Then we just leave the roads altogether.
有多远开多远 我们开去森林 然后步行离开
Drive as far as we can into the forest and we go on foot from there.
你没明白我的意思
You're missing the point.
拜托 别对着我发疯了 好吗 Dana 你现在是我的一切
Please, do not go nuts on me, okay, Dana? You're all I've got, now.
我很好
I'm okay.
很好 因为我需要你冷静下来
Good, okay, 'cause I need you calm.
好的 不管发生了什么 我们要在
Okay, no matter what happens, we gotta stay..
上帝啊 那个可真近
Goddamn, that was close!
耶 终于成功了
Yeah, photo-fucking-finish.
我不明白
I don't understand.
你们在庆祝
You're celebrating?
他们在庆祝 我在喝酒
They're celebrating. I'm drinking.
但是她还活着
But she's still alive.
这个仪式怎么完成
How can the ritual be complete?
处女的死亡可有可无
The virgin's death is optional, as long as it's last.
最重要的是她活着遭受的事情
Main thing is that she suffers.
她做的事情
That she did.
感觉真奇怪
It's so strange.
我开始支持她了
I'm actually rooting for this girl.
她那么的顽强
She's got so much heart.
她经历了那么多的痛苦
And you think of all the pain and the..
龙舌兰是我的女神 我的女神
Tequila is my lady! My lady!
进来 伙计们 进来 欢迎你们
Come on in, guys! Come on in. You're welcome.
龙舌兰 在黑暗之中的光亮
Tequila! From darkness, there is light!
我希望我能做到你所做的
I wish that I could do what you do.
-哦 上帝  -没错 这是大师级的
-Oh, my God.  -Yeah, it's masterful.
我不知道 今晚不太顺 我不知道
I don't know. Tonight was solid. I don't know.
你在开玩笑吗 经典的结局 当货车冲进湖里的时候
Are you kidding? Classic denouement. When the van hits the lake..
我尖叫了
I screamed.
然后水涌了进来 还有僵尸们
And the water rushing in, and the zombies..
要是有个男人鱼就更酷了
just think it would've been cooler with a merman.
你觉得我们能不能拿到加班奖金
Do you know if we get the overtime bonus on this one?
会计就在那里 问他们
Accounting's over there. Ask them.
我不需要 我已经知道答案了
I don't need to. I already know the answer.
我只是实习生
I'm an intern.
我还不够资格拿加班奖金
So I don't qualify for OT.
你喜欢芭蕾 很有意思
It's funny that you like the ballet..
因为我正好有两张你喜欢的
because I happen to have two tickets to your favorite..
你个蠢货
You knuckleheads.
隧道那里你害的我差点得心脏病
You almost gave me a heart attack with that tunnel.
就像我说的 那不是我们的错 我们没有收到指令
Like I said, it wasn't our fault. We didn't get the order.
我只是刁难一下你们
I'm just giving you a hard time.
来吧 拥抱一下
Come on. Give us a hug.
不 说真的 那不是我们的错
No, seriously. That wasn't our fault.
那里出现了故障 楼上的电力有问题
There was a glitch. Power re-route from upstairs.
你说什么 楼上
What do you mean, upstairs?
把他妈的音乐关掉
Turn the fucking music off.
你好
Hello?
那不可能 所有的事情都是按照指令做的
That's impossible. Everything was done within the guidelines.
处女是唯一一个
The virgin's the only one..
不 我不是在质疑您
No. I am not doubting you.
哪一个
Which one?
-Marty  -嗨
-Marty.  -Hi.
Dana 过来
Dana, come on.
Marty 等等
Marty. Wait.
我们要进到坟墓里面吗
We're going in the grave?
Dana 快过来
Dana, come on!
这里是哪里
What is this place?
我不得不用小铲子肢解了那个家伙
Yeah. I had to dismember that guy with a trowel.
你怎么样
What have you been up to?
其他人都死了 是吧
Nobody else, huh?
好吧 我猜到了
Yeah, I figured.
你猜到了所有的事情
You figured everything.
不 不是全部
Oh, not at all.
但是 我的确知道一些事情
But, I do know some stuff.
就在
As in..
这是一部电梯
It's an elevator.
有人派了这些死尸来抓我们
Somebody sent those dead fucks up here to get us.
现在 这里面没有控制电梯的地方 但是这有个维修装置
Now, there's no controls inside, but there's maintenance overrides in there.
我想我能让它下去
And I think I can get it to go down.
我们要下去吗
Do we wanna go down?
否则还能去哪里
Where else are we gonna go?
过来 进来
Come on. Get in.
快点
Come on!
去他妈的僵尸胳膊
Fucking zombie arm.
哦 该死
Oh, shit.
这是我们选的
We chose.
什么 什么
What? What?
妈的
Fuck!
我们对付的那些鬼东西
All that shit we were playing with.
他们让我们做了选择
They made us choose.
他们让我们选择怎么死
They made us choose how we die.
我们看见他们进了入口 他们肯定在这之中的一个电梯里
We saw them go down the access drop. They have to be in one of these.
内部安保可以
Internal security can..
我才不在乎这是不是协议的一部分 你他妈疯了么
I don't care if it's not protocol. Are you fucking high?
是那个白痴 别碰那个女孩
It's the fool! Do not touch the girl.
如果他比她活得久 这件事就毁了
If he outlives her, this whole thing goes to hell.
先干掉他
Take him out first.
清理部门说之前的队伍漏掉了那群孩子其中一处藏身地
Cleanup says the prep team missed one of the kid's stashes.
他在吸收的东西能够让他对我们的东西免疫
Whatever he's been smoking's been immunizing him to all our shit.
这个消息对我们一点帮助也没有 什么
How does that help us right now? What?
不 要是你有确信能杀掉他们的方法 把她也干掉
No, if you have a confirmed kill, take her out, too.
那里
There.
3606.
有了
Gotcha.
把他们带下来
Bring 'em down.
从电梯里出来 从电梯里出来
Step out of the elevator! Step out of the elevator!
-你为什么要杀我们  -出来 女孩出来
-Why are you trying to kill us?  - Step out! Just the girl!
-什么  -只有我
-What?  -Just me?
快照做
Do it!
干得好 僵尸胳膊
Good work, zombie arm.
你们不应该来这里
You shouldn't be here.
事情不应该是这样
This should've gone differently.
应该速战速决
Ended more quickly.
我只能想象你们的痛苦和困惑
I can only imagine your pain and confusion.
但是记住这点
But know this.
现在发生在你们身上的事情
What's happening to you is part of something bigger.
远远超出你们的想象
Something older than anything known.
你已经见过了可怕的生物
You've seen horrible things.
一支噩梦般怪物的军队
An army of nightmare creatures.
但是跟之前发生的事情相比 和下面的生物相比
But they are nothing compared to what came before.
他们根本不值一提
What lies below.
我们的任务就是安抚古老的生物
It's our task to placate the ancient ones.
你们的任务就是献祭
As it's yours to be offered up to them.
原谅我们
Forgive us.
让我们结束这一切吧
And let us get it over with.
快 进那个房间
Come on. Go in that room.
噩梦怪物的军队 哈
Army of nightmares, huh?
让我们开始狂欢吧
Let's get this party started.
停火
Hold fire!
哦 该死
Oh, shit.
前进 前进 前进
Go! Go! Go!
领队Truman呼叫安保指挥中心
Lead officer Truman to security command.
请立即增援 黑色警报 重复 黑色警报
Requesting immediate reinforcements. Code black. I repeat, code black.
你们他妈的上哪儿去了
Where the fuck are you guys?
12区 失控 8区 失控
Sector 12, down. Sector 8, down.
3区 失控 上帝啊
Sector 3, down. Jesus Christ!
为什么防御系统不起作用 那该死的气体哪里去了
Why aren't the defenses working? Where's the fucking gas?
有什么东西咬坏了接线
Something chewed through the connections in the utility shaft.
-什么东西  -恐怖的东西
-Something which? - Something scary!
北边出口已经封锁 你们不能去那里
The north exit is blocked. You can't go there.
快 快 快
Go, go, go!
该死的 我们没时间了
Fuck! We're running out of time!
这里被封锁了 我在试图绕过去
It's on lockdown, I'm trying to bypass.
Hadley
Hadley!
哦 拜托
Oh, come on!
是你
It's you.
不 不 不 求你了 求你了
No, no, no. Please, please.
杀了他
Kill him.
好了 Dana 过来
Okay, Dana, come on.
Dana
Dana.
过来 用枪更方便
Here. It's easier with this.
看看这些
Look at these.
有五个人
Five of them.
这些都是什么
What are they?
我们
Us.
我应该像你一样事前看过的
I should have seen it like you did.
这是仪式的一部分
This is part of a ritual.
仪式里用来献祭的吗
A ritual sacrifice?
很好
Great.
把一个人绑到石头上 拿把漂亮匕首 一堆穿着长袍的怪人
You tie someone to a stone, get a fancy dagger and a bunch of robes.
- 需要那么复杂吗  - 不
- Is that that complicated?   - No.
这个很简单
It's simple.
他们想要的不是我们的命
They don't just want to see us killed.
他们想要我们受到惩罚
They want to see us punished.
为什么而受罚
Punished for what?
因为年轻
For being young.
尽管在每种文化里都不一样
It's different in every culture.
随着时间流逝规则也有所改变了
And it has changed over the years..
但年轻的生命总是必不可少的环节
but it has always required youth.
这儿至少有五个
There must be at least five.
那个妓女
The whore.
她已经堕落了
She's corrupted.
她是最先死的
She dies first.
学者
The scholar.
傻大个
The fool.
他们都受过罪 最后又死于...
All suffer and die at the hands of..
无论他们曾经历过多可怕的事情
whatever horror they have raised..
都已经过去了 现在是死是活
leaving the last, to live or die..
要让命运做决定了
.. as fate decides.
最后的处女
The virgin.
我
Me?
我就是那个处女
Virgin?
我们只能利用手头的人选了
We work with what we have.
但如果你不能圆满完成仪式呢
But what if you don't pull it off?
他们就回来
They rise.
谁会来
Who does?
我们下面的到底是什么
What's beneath us?
古老的生物
The ancient ones.
它们的神曾经统领过地球
The gods that used to rule the Earth.
一旦它们接受了我们的献祭 就会重回地底
As long as they accept our sacrifice, they remain below.
但是这之前的仪式全都失败了
But the other rituals have all failed.
再有八分钟太阳就会升起
The sun is coming up in eight minutes.
如果你活到那个时候 这世界就完了
If you live to see it, the world will end.
也许这世界就该这么完蛋
Maybe that's the way it should be.
如果你杀了我那些朋友就是为了自己活命
If you've got to kill all my friends to survive..
也许现在是时候遭报应了
maybe it's time for a change.
我们不是在讨论道德问题
We're not talking about change.
这关系到一个星球的存活 关系到这个星球上每一个人的性命
We're talking about the agonizing death of every human soul on the planet.
包括你
Including you.
你可以和他们一起死
You can die with them..
或者为了拯救他们而牺牲
or you can die for them.
天 现在两样听上去都挺不错了
Gosh, they're both so enticing.
整个世界 Marty
The whole world, Marty.
现在世界的命运掌握在你手中 Dana
Is in your hands, Dana.
没有别的方法了
There is no other way.
你必须坚强
You have to be strong.
是啊 Dana
Yeah, Dana..
你现在觉得有力量了吗
you feeling strong?
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我也一样
So am I.
Marty
Marty..
Marty!
嘿
Hey.
你知道吗
You know..
我想Curt从来就没什么表弟
I don't think Curt even has a cousin.
你怎么样了？
How are you?
感觉快要死了
Going away.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我很抱歉 我差点就对你开枪了
I'm so sorry I almost shot you.
我也许根本就不用
I probably wouldn't have.
嘿 不 不用这样
Hey, no. No.
我完全懂你的意思
I totally get it.
对不起我让你被一个狼人攻击 而现在世界末日要来了
I'm sorry I let you get attacked by a werewolf and then ended the world.
不
No.
嘿 你是对的
Hey, you were right.
人类...
Humanity...
是时候试试让其他物种统治世界了
It's time to give someone else a chance.
强大的邪神
Giant evil gods.
我真希望能亲眼见见它们
I wish I could've seen them.
我懂
I know.
这样这个周末就算有意思了
That would have been a fun weekend.
－＝蓝光电影网＝－
blu-raydisc.tv